(Sheldon:)that ferments fruit
in order to become intoxicated.
(Sheldon:)Can you guess what the other is?
Hint: sometimes they pack
the alcohol
(Sheldon:)in their trunks.
(Penny:)Monkeys.
(Sheldon:)When does a monkey
have a trunk?
(Penny:)When a suitcase just won't do.
(Sheldon:)Mmm, all right.
(Sheldon:)It would appear as if alcohol
(Sheldon:)is playing keep-away
with your intelligence.
(Raj:)Good night.
(Sheldon:)Please note,
it is now past 10:00 p.m.
(Sheldon:)Per our roommate agreement,
kindly refrain
(Sheldon:)from raucous laughter,
(Sheldon:)clinking of glasses,
and celebratory gunfire.
(Penny:)Okay...
(Penny:)explain something to me.
(Penny:)You watch Leonard put up with
that guy for years and years.
(Penny:)What has to break inside
your brain for you to think,
"Oh, Krishna, I've got to
get me some of that"?